<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Geeks in Progress</title>
    <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Geeks in Progress</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Geeks in Progress - All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 12:40:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://geeksinprogress.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re Not A Console...Yet...</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-37/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 12:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-37/</guid>
      <description>This week on Geeks in Progress: Batman fights Superman, rumors of Playstation 4.5 and Nintendo NX abound, Microsoft wants to cooperate on cross-platform play, The Division breaks sales records, and more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh God, You&#39;re Going To Be One of Those Smart House People!</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-36/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 08:47:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-36/</guid>
      <description>This week on Geeks in Progress: Microsoft is ending its fixed console hardware, The Division launches, Everquest Next is cancelled, Guild Wars 2&amp;rsquo;s game director leaves the company, and more; we discuss key resellers, and progression systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Action Movie Schlock Version of World War I</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-35/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Feb 2016 09:10:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-35/</guid>
      <description>This week on Geeks in Progress: Yuuuge episode! Deadpool releases to commercial success (spoilers within), Gametrailers closes, a potential Hideo Kojima/Guillermo del Toro partnership emerges, Battlefield 5 is rumored to be a WWI shooter, Quantum Break comes to PC, we blow a weekend on the Division open Beta, and more! We discuss where Marvel and DC stand as regards movies and television, the current trend of AAA games releasing as unfinished products, and what the hell Microsoft is doing with its exclusives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Galactic Ambulance</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-34/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 05:34:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-34/</guid>
      <description>This week on Geeks in Progress: Matt tells a story, Kurt tells a joke, Chris steals a bit from John Mulaney, The Division launches its closed beta, Steam begins its Lunar New Year sale, and a Kickstarter team blows its budget on hookers and drugs; we discuss the state of early access games, and the games we&amp;rsquo;ve played during the podcast&amp;rsquo;s hiatus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Podcast is Worth...One Quarter Portion!</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-33/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-33/</guid>
      <description>The Sunshine and Frank Podcast is now the Geeks in Progress Podcast! This week, we give our reviews of Star Wars: the Force Awakens, and discuss other movies releasing or announced in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We All Have Our Own Hole</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-32/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2015 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-32/</guid>
      <description>This week on Sunshine and Frank: E3 2015! Bethesda&amp;rsquo;s Fallout 4 gets annouced, Bungie&amp;rsquo;s announcement suffers fallout, Dishonoured 2 gets revealed, FFVII gets a remake, we (finally) get a glimpse at what the Division is all about, and more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blood, Sweat, and Midi-chlorians</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-31/</guid>
      <description>This week on Sunshine and Frank: Evolve gets released, Sony Online Entertainment gets sold to Daybreak, the &amp;ldquo;New 3DS&amp;rdquo; comes out, and we look forward to the new Star Wars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>He&#39;s Not Marvelous, He&#39;s DC&#39;ous</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-30/</guid>
      <description>This week on Sunshine and Frank: Matt loses his sniper rifle, Netflix is rumoured to be working on a Legend of Zelda TV series, Nintendo changes its Youtube policy, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That Time I Spent $65 On A Pretend Spaceship</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2015 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-29/</guid>
      <description>This week on Sunshine and Frank: H1Z1 launches in Early Access, Matt starts a Star Citizen stream, Guild Wars 2 and FFXIV get expansions, Elder Scrolls Online goes buy-to-play; we discuss zombie survival games, betting in esports, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You, 3 Characters, and a Tree, and Some Stairs</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2015 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-28/</guid>
      <description>This week on Sunshine and Frank: We discuss the games we enjoyed playing in 2014, and the games we look forward to playing in the near future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Games Were So Much Cooler When I Was 14</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2014 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-27/</guid>
      <description>This week on Sunshine and Frank: Matt gets an Xbox One, Xbox Live and PSN get DDOS&amp;rsquo;d by the Lizard Squad, Halo 3 ODST&amp;rsquo;s campaign is getting ported to Xbox One, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Give You the Jericho...Times Six!</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2014 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-26/</guid>
      <description>This week on Sunshine and Frank: Respawn Entertainment&amp;rsquo;s lead hints future games will be on Steam, Mechwarrior Online finally releases its community warfare patch, the Steam Winter Sale is live, MGSV: Ground Zeroes releases, Metal Gear Online gets a trailer, and more; we discuss gamification and tabletop gaming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>She&#39;s Learned How to Weaponize Her Aura</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2014 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-25/</guid>
      <description>This week on Sunshine and Frank: NJ is a wasteland, RSI talks multi-crew ships and customizable ship interiors, Street Fighter V is announced, Broken Age 2 is delayed to early 2015, Kaia (and Stephen Colbert) defend the new lightsaber, Chris gushes about Child of Light, and much more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andy Dwyer, Dinosaur Hunter</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2014 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-24/</guid>
      <description>This week on Sunshine and Frank: trailers are released for Jurassic World and some other nerd movie, Nintendo patents emulators for its devices, controversy erupts over a map exploit in Dreamhack Winter&amp;rsquo;s CS:GO tournament, and more; we discuss the future of consoles, new interfaces, and dedicated casters vs pro player casters in esports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I AM the boarding craft!</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2014 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-23/</guid>
      <description>This week on Sunshine and Frank: World of Warcraft gains back 2.6 million subscribers, Red vs Blue wraps up its 12th season, Far Cry 4 releases, and more; we discuss Star Citizen&amp;rsquo;s damage model, permadeath, and what happens to your character when you get captured.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sounds Like You Want to Go to a Rave, Dog</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-22/</guid>
      <description>This week on Sunshine and Frank: Halo: The MCC has multiplayer issues, CoD: Advanced Warfare releases (and is actually pretty good!), Assassin&amp;rsquo;s Creed Unity has technical issues, Matt buys a flight stick, Blizzard teases Overwatch and Legacy of the Void at Blizzcon, and more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Fed Bananas To Homeless People</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2014 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-21/</guid>
      <description>This week on Sunshine and Frank: Matt binges on board games and Munchkin Quest, while Chris spends the weekend in DC; new Smash Bros. characters get announced, Microsoft talks plans for Minecraft, Dark Souls switches from GFWL to Steamworks, and more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mikey, Just Keep Pressing B.</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2014 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-20/</guid>
      <description>This week on Sunshine and Frank: Matt and Kaia go to Comic-Con, Chris gets hands-on time with the Oculus Rift, Star Citizen releases landing and planetside footage, Kaia plays Hyrule Warriors, and much more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aragorn Effs Up Everything: The Game</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2014 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-19/</guid>
      <description>This week on Sunshine and Frank: Matt loves Shadow of Mordor, Kurt plays Destiny, Microsoft demos &amp;ldquo;room alive&amp;rdquo;, Smash Bros. 4 is released and more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Developed By Astronauts</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2014 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-18/</guid>
      <description>This week on Sunshine and Frank: Our shortest episode ever!: S Matt checks out The Vanishing of Ethan Carter, Blizzard cancels it&amp;rsquo;s in-development MMO &amp;ldquo;Titan&amp;rdquo;, Matt finishes Red Orchestra 2 bootcamp, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Star! One Star! Terrible Game!  AGHBFBPBP</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2014 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-17/</guid>
      <description>This week on Sunshine and Frank: Microsoft buys Minecraft, Destiny and Archeage are released, Microsoft tests video games played from the web browser, and Guild Wars 2 releases its September 2014 Feature Pack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All the Cool Science Fiction is From the 80s</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-16/</guid>
      <description>This week on Sunshine and Frank: Guardians of the Galaxy is hot shit, Piranha Games takes money and makes a new game, Matt tries Star Citizen, and WB announces a digital distribution platform; we discuss old school sci-fi, space operas, and the Mass Effect trilogy (spoilers!).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Damn it, Bobby! Shoulder Buttons?</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-15/</guid>
      <description>This week on Sunshine and Frank: A buyout of Twitch is (actually) confirmed, a Youtuber gets &amp;ldquo;swatted&amp;rdquo;, Star Citizen has a free trial, Nintendo announces a New 3DS, and Planetary Annihilation gets a release date. We discuss PC Gamer&amp;rsquo;s top 10 PC games, the appeal of Archeage, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Were the Dee Dee of the Campaign</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-14/</guid>
      <description>This week on Sunshine and Frank: Matt throws money at RSI, every game developer under the sun gets DDOS&amp;rsquo;d, Obsidian licenses Pathfinder, and DnD 5e is released. We discuss digital download statistics, changing gaming demographics, system exclusives, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Put It On Auto-Horsey</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-13/</guid>
      <description>This week on Sunshine and Frank: Matt gets hooked on Hearthstone, Kurt puts it on Auto-horsey, and Moose disconnects and hopes no one notices. We discuss our favorite trailers from Gamescom (Quantum Break, Silent Hills, MGS 5, Star Citizen), military mecha anime, moral choice systems, the state of emulators, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Can&#39;t Confirm Or Deny</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-12/</guid>
      <description>This week on Sunshine and Frank: Matt is on vacation, Twitch.tv adopts a new Youtube-like audio recognition and take-down system, Crytek speaks publicly about its financial situation, Valve soft-launches Source Engine 2, preorders are down and digital sales are up; we discuss Twitch acquisition rumors, Jedi Academy mods, hudless games, and much more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Being A Backwards Kid</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-10/</guid>
      <description>This week on Sunshine and Frank: The consoles can&amp;rsquo;t even handle Star Citizen, a new Thor hits comic books, Occulus Rift is a home for space sims, Super Smash Bros. characters get announced, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Two Dollar Piece of Cardboard</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-9/</guid>
      <description>This week on Sunshine and Frank: Civilization: Beyond Earth is announced, Crytek has financial trouble, a former Valve contractor posts a pessimistic view of the coming VR trend; we discuss Valiant Hearts, the PC graphics arms race, augmented reality and driving, the decline of online gaming communites, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bear Tactics</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-8/</guid>
      <description>This week on Sunshine and Frank: a new Space Hulk game gets announced, Occulus acquire Carbon Design Group; we discuss the state of the Kinect, speedruns, simulator games, and more. more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Very Obvious Skateboard Shaped Package</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-7/</guid>
      <description>This week on Sunshine and Frank: Quebec cuts tax breaks for game studios, Watchdogs gets a graphics mod, the Steam Summer Sale arrives, we discuss E3 promises and our favorite horror games, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You See That Mountain Over There? You Can Climb It!</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-6/</guid>
      <description>This week on Sunshine and Frank we discuss the games we were most impressed with at E3. Shadow of Mordor, The Division, Rainbow Six: Siege, Hyrule Warriors, the Halo Series, Evolve, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PrE3!</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-5/</guid>
      <description>This week on Sunshine and Frank we discuss Steam Early Access, before going into the games we are looking forward to seeing at the coming week&amp;rsquo;s E3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Might Be Your Mods!</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-4/</guid>
      <description>This week on Sunshine and Frank we talk about the recent Nintendo news on Youtube, Watchdogs and some old classics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Earn Your Way!</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-3/</guid>
      <description>This week on Sunshine and Frank we talk about the latest update to Titanfall&amp;rsquo;s matchmaking! As well as a game review of Dark Souls 2 and how it stacks up against the old game!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People Want Big!</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-2/</guid>
      <description>This week on Sunshine and Frank we dive into Star Citizen, Assassin&amp;rsquo;s Creed and the next generation of consoles!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Little Podcast!</title>
      <link>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geeksinprogress.com/episodes/episode-1/</guid>
      <description>###Our Little Podcast!
Join Frank and the crew on our first podcast as we talk about Oculus, MMO&amp;rsquo;s, Mech Warrior Online, and Star Wars!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>